Guide to the British-American Tobacco Company Records, 1842-1929
British-American Tobacco Company records 1842-1929
British-American Tobacco Company.
372 Items
Duke University. David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. There may be a 48-hour delay in obtaining these materials.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The British-American Tobacco Company Records were purchased by Duke University in 1945.
Subject Headings
These are searchable subject entries for this collection. Performing a search on these subjects in the Duke University Libraries online catalog will bring up other related research materials.
Bland Tobacco Company (Petersburg, Va.).
British-American Tobacco Company
Cameron and Cameron
D.B. Tennant and Company
David Dunlop (Firm).
Export Leaf Tobacco Company
T.C. Williams Company
Petersburg (Va.)--Industries
Tobacco industry -- United States
Virginia -- Economic conditions
Collection Overview
The British-American Tobacco Company, Ltd., was established in 1902 by an agreement between the Imperial Tobacco Co. of Great Britain and its rivals, the American Tobacco Co. and its associates. These firms divided the world's market for manufactured tobacco products, and British-American took over trade with those territories not reserved to Imperial and American, that is, the export business everywhere outside Great Britain, Ireland, the Isle of Man, Cuba, and the U. S. and its overseas dependencies. Ownership of British-American was divided between its parent companies, American holding substantially two-thirds of the stock. The headquarters was located in London, England, and the office at 111 5th Ave. in New York City handled the purchase of leaf and manufacturing in the U. S.
This collection concerns British-American's business at Petersburg, Virginia, which included the branch under its own name and also the operations of its subsidiaries and predecessors. In 1903 the company acquired the formerly independent export businesses of the T. C. Williams Co., David Dunlop, and the Cameron family who were then the largest exporters of manufactured tobacco. They also had sales within the United States, so some domestic business is represented. British-American owned all of the stock of T. C. Williams and two-thirds of Dunlop's, both of these subsidiaries continuing to function under their own names, chiefly as producers of plug tobacco. However, the manufacturing of their brands was concentrated in a single bonded warehouse at Petersburg, a situation reflected in many account books that combine records of Dunlop, Williams, and British-American. There are also several volumes from the Bland Tobacco Co. of Petersburg and the Export Leaf Tobacco Co., the latter a subsidiary of British-American that functioned as its buying agency in the U. S. Further information about these companies is given below where their records are listed. A useful source for the early history of British-American is the U. S. Bureau of Corporations, Report of the Commissioner of Corporations on the Tobacco Industry (Washington, 1909). A folder of information about the companies and their owners is filed with the Guide in a box at the beginning of the collection. The Tobacco Collection includes examples of advertising.
This set of 367 account books represents the operations of British-American at Petersburg primarily during its first twenty years, 1903-1923, of which the first ten years have the more abundant records. The accounts of one subsidiary, David Dunlop, begin in 1842, continue into the 1920's, and constitute the most substantial group within the collection. Records of T. C. Williams are confined almost entirely to the period after 1903 when it was British-American's subsidiary, although the firm originated in the 1850's. Cameron & Cameron also began in the 1850's, but its records are limited to the last twelve years of its existence, 1892-1904. There are also a few volumes for the Export Leaf Tobacco Co., the Bland Tobacco Co., and William Cameron & Brother.
The account books are extensive and include significant records, but they are quite incomplete. Only David Dunlop has a considerable series of ledgers and journals. There are no minutes from meetings of directors or stockholders. The strength of the collection before 1903 is in the Dunlop records with the addition after 1892 of some from Cameron & Cameron, principally letterpress books. After 1903 there are elaborate cost, production, sales, and stock records for British-American, Dunlop, and T. C. Williams. Correspondence is very limited but includes some important material, there being volumes for David Dunlop in 1842-1846 and 1904-1906, T. C. Williams in 1903-1906, and Cameron & Cameron in 1895-1903.
Contents of Collection
- David Dunlop
  The Dunlop family of Petersburg, Virginia, engaged in the manufacture and export of tobacco for more than a century, their interests dating back at least to 1820 when James Dunlop built a large factory. His brothers Robert and David also were involved in manufacturing, and the business of David Dunlop and his descendants is the one represented here by an important, although incomplete, set of records. The proprietorship of the firm varied over the years and is not always clearly defined in the existing records. The Letter Book, 1842-1846, indicates that David Dunlop was operating under his own name. He was also a partner with his brother in the firm of John A. Dunlop & Co. of Louisville, Kentucky, with whom he corresponded. A brother was in the Petersburg Company of Dunlop & Tennant (letter of July 24, 1844). The letters indicate considerable business with Great Britain, Ireland, the Netherlands, and Belgium.
  After the Civil War the succeeding David Dunlop (ca. 1841-1902) was associated with David B. Tennant in the firm of D. B. Tennant & Co. that operated until the latter's death in 1885, at which time he was reputed to be Petersburg's wealthiest citizen. David Dunlop continued the business under his own name and was at the time of his death one of the largest exporters of manufactured tobacco in the U. S. His products were principally plug and twist, according to Connorton's Tobacco Brand Directory of the United States in 1887 and 1899. His son David Dunlop sold the business to British-American in 1903 when it was registered in New Jersey as David Dunlop (Incorporated). He was president of the new firm and both he and R. L. Dunlop were directors. The corporation continued into the 1920s and possibly later. Information about the company can be found in: David Dunlop's obituary in Tobacco, 33, No. 26 (Oct. 31, 1902), p. 2; Joseph Clarke Robert, The Tobacco Kingdom (Durham, N. C., 1938), pp. 186-187 (which also includes an illustration of an advertising poster); and in the Report of the Commissioner of Corporations on the Tobacco Industry (Washington, 1909). The first entry in D. B. Tennant & Co.'s Journal, 1867-1880, and those of Jan. 1, 1886 and Jan. 2, 1889, in the Journal, 1880-1890, as well as other entries, document Dunlop's association with Mr. Tennant.
  The Tobacco Collection includes one or more examples of Dunlop's advertisements.
  The records of David Dunlop extend for almost ninety years, and, although incomplete, they constitute the most substantial group within the collection - and the only one that dates well back into the nineteenth century. A ledger and journal of 1847-1856 and a letter book of 1842-1846 (including an invoice book, 1842-1847) are important volumes from the antebellum period. The letter book records the difficulties of businessmen during the war scare over the Oregon Question in 1845-1846 and Dunlop's reaction to that issue and to President Polk. This volume is also valuable for comment about crop conditions, marketing, etc. After the war D. B. Tennant & Co. is represented notably by its journals of 1867-1890, bills of exchange of 1870-1887, and payroll records of 1878-1879 and 1883-1886. The accounts for David Dunlop during 1885-1903 are the best preserved set. The important ledgers and journals are complete for this period, and the payroll books are almost complete. There are also broken runs of invoice and shipping books, bills of exchange, and others. The strength of the records for the two decades after 1903 is in the elaborate cost, production, and sales records in the cost sheets, details of cost, and general statements. The Leaf Department also has ledgers, journals, and books for statements, insurance, and warehouse storage.
  The volume of General Statements, 1904-1905, includes an inventory of Dunlop for Dec. 31, 1904. This inventory is published in Nannie M. Tilley, The Bright-Tobacco Industry, 1860-1929, (Chapel Hill, 1948), pp. 690-696.
  A folder of miscellaneous papers, 1902-1922, includes a few accounts from Dunlop. The folder is filed in the first box of the collection.
  - David Dunlop
    - Ledger, 1847-1856 (Volume 1)
    - Journal, 1847, Jan.-Jan., 1856 (Volume 2)
      (Available on microfilm only. Original in Virginia Historical Society at Richmond.)
    - Letter Book, 1842 Nov.-1846 May, & Invoice Book, 1842 Jan.-1847 Jan. (Volume 3)
  - D. B. Tennant & Co.
    - Journal, 1867 Feb.-1880 Apr. (Volume 4)
    - Journal, 1880 May-1890 Dec. (Volume 5)
    - Invoice Book, 1882 Sept.-1885 Dec. (Volume 6)
    - Time Book, 1878 Jan.-1879 Sept. (Volume 7)
      (Including Tobacco Accounts, Factory No. 2, 1878-1886)
    - Payroll Book, 1883 Sept.-1886 Jan. (Volume 8)
    - Bills of Exchange, 1870 Jan.-1872 June (Volume 9)
    - Bills of Exchange, 1874 July-1876 July (Volume 10)
    - Bills of Exchange, 1878 Feb.-1880 Mar. (Volume 11)
    - Bills of Exchange, 1886 Jan.-1887 June (Volume 12)
    - Drafts, 1877 Jan.-1880 Dec. (Volume 13)
    - Checkbook, 1868 Sept.-1870 May (Volume 14)
    - Checkbook, 1875 July-1876 July (Volume 15)
    - Checkbook, 1876 July-1877 June (Volume 16)
    - Checkbook, 1877 June-1878 June (Volume 17)
    - Checkbook, 1879 June-1880 Sept. (Volume 18)
    - Checkbook, 1882 Apr.-Oct. (Volume 19)
    - Checkbook, 1883 Oct.-1884 Sept. (Volume 20)
    - Checkbook, 1884 Sept.-1885 June (Volume 21)
  - David Dunlop
    - Ledger, 1885-1904 (Volume 22)
    - Personal Ledger, 1902-1904 (Volume 23)
    - Ledger for Estate of David Dunlop, 1902-1903 (Volume 24)
      (Also available on microfilm)
    - Journal, 1885 Dec.-1891 Nov. (Volume 25)
    - Journal, 1891 Nov.-1896 July (Volume 26)
    - Journal, 1896 July-1899 June (Volume 27)
    - Journal, 1899 June-1904 May (Volume 28)
    - Personal Journal, 1902 Nov.-1904 May (Volume 29)
    - Journal for Estate of David Dunlop, 1902 Nov.-1903 Nov. (Volume 30)
    - Cashbook, 1899 June-1902 Nov. (Volume 31)
    - Payroll Book, 1886 Jan.-1887 Mar. (Volume 32)
    - Payroll Book, 1887 Mar.-Sept. (Volume 33)
    - Payroll Book 1889 Jan.-Oct. (Volume 34)
    - Payroll Book, 1889 Oct.-1890 Dec. (Volume 35)
    - Payroll Book, 1891 (Volume 36)
    - Payroll Book, 1892 (Volume 37)
    - Payroll Book, 1893 Jan.-1894 Jan. (Volume 38)
    - Payroll Book, 1894 Jan.-Dec. (Volume 39)
    - Payroll Book, 1895 (Volume 40)
    - Payroll Book, 1897 (Volume 41)
    - Payroll Book, 1898 (Volume 42)
    - Payroll Book, 1899 (Volume 43)
    - Payroll Book, 1900 (Volume 44)
    - Payroll Book, 1901 Jan.-1902 Jan. (Volume 45)
    - Payroll Book, 1902 Jan.-Nov. (Volume 46)
    - Payroll Book, 1902 Nov.-1904 Dec. (Volume 314)
    - Time Book, 1901 Oct.-1905 Oct. (Volume 47)
      (Gap in records: 1904 Aug.-1905 June; records of 1903-1904 are from Old St, Wythe St., and West Hill factories)
    - Purchase Book, 1886 Jan.-1895 May (Volume 48)
    - Tobacco Received, 1897 Oct.-1902 Oct. (Volume 49)
    - Invoice Book, 1886 Jan.-1890 Aug. (Volume 50)
    - Invoice Book, 1890 Aug.-1894 July (Volume 51)
    - Invoice Book, 1897 May-1901 June (Volume 52)
    - Invoice Book, 1901 June-1902 Sept. (Volume 52.1)
    - Prizing Record Book, 1899-1903 (Volume 53)
    - Shipping Book, 1887 (Volume 54)
    - Shipping Book, 1894 (Volume 55)
    - Shipping Book, 1897 (Volume 56)
    - Shipping Book, 1900 (Volume 57)
    - Shipping Book, 1902 Nov.-1903 Dec. (Volume 58)
    - Shipments to C. R. Somervail & Co., 1901 (Volume 59)
      (Including also Free Materials, 1902-1907, and Insurance Charges, 1907-1908)
    - Bills of Exchange, 1890 July-1891 Nov. (Volume 60)
    - Bills of Exchange, 1891 Nov.-1894 Nov. (Volume 61)
    - Bills of Exchange, 1902 Feb.-1903 Sept. (Volume 62)
    - Drafts, 1886 Jan.-1892 Dec. (Volume 63)
    - Checkbook, 1886 Dec.-1887 Nov. (Volume 64)
    - Checkbook, 1887 Nov.-1888 July (Volume 65)
    - Checkbook, 1888 Oct.-1891 Mar. (Volume 66)
    - Checkbook, 1892 Aug.-1893 May (Volume 67)
    - Checkbook, 1894 Feb.-Oct. (Volume 68)
    - Checkbook, 1895 June-1896 Jan. (Volume 69)
    - Checkbook, 1896 Aug.-1897 Apr. (Volume 70)
    - Checkbook, 1898 June-1899 Jan. (Volume 71)
    - Checkbook, 1899 Sept.-1900 Apr. (Volume 72)
    - Checkbook, 1900 Apr.-Aug. (Volume 73)
    - Checkbook, 1902 Sept.-1911 Dec. (Volume 74)
- Remarks on the Companies and Their Accounts After 1903
  The structure and records of the companies after 1903 are complicated by the fact that British-American concentrated the manufacture of the brands of Dunlop, Cameron, Williams, and its other acquisitions in a single bonded warehouse at Petersburg
  (Report of the Commissioner of Corporations on the Tobacco Industry (Washington, 1909), p. 361
  also noted in Williams' Letterpress Book, June- Sept., 1903, p. 695). This situation is reflected in the account books. For some types of records there are separate volumes for Dunlop,; Williams, and British-American. In other cases their accounts are combined, sometimes clearly labeled and sometimes not. Dunlop's Cost Sheets and Details of Cost include some figures for the brands of Williams and British-American, but the volumes are labeled as belonging to Dunlop. Some volumes clearly contain statistics for all three companies. So there are lists below of account books for Dunlop,; Williams,; British-American, and combinations of them, as well as for lesser groups such as the Export Leaf Tobacco Co. and the Bland Tobacco Co.
  The situation is further complicated by divisions within Dunlop. Several series of accounts belonged to its Leaf Department, and they are segregated accordingly. However, the volumes were not always carefully labeled, and some books not listed for the Leaf Department may actually relate to it. It is not the purpose of this inventory to determine the exact operational structure of the businesses, especially since their records are so incomplete.
  It is always possible that some unlabeled volumes have been incorrectly placed in this inventory, and the researcher should apply appropriate caution in using them. Further, titles of account books varied, sometimes in the same series, or were incomplete or absent altogether, so some titles supplied here may not technically be entirely accurate.
- David Dunlop (Incorporated)
  - Letterpress Books
    - Letterpress Book, 1904 Aug.-Oct. (Volume 75)
      (Includes T. C. Williams, 1905 Jan.-Feb.)
    - Letterpress Book, 1906 Jan.-July (Volume 76)
      (Includes a few letters of T. C. Williams and Cameron & Cameron)
    - Letterpress Book, 1905 Sept.-1906 June (Volume 77)
      (Addressed to David Dunlop, New York)
    - Letterpress Book, 1906 July-Sept. (Volume 286)
      (Included in Invoice Book, 1907-1908, of Dunlop,; Williams, and British-American)
  - Cost Sheets
    The Cost Sheets contain a variety of reports, often monthly, of costs, trial balances, expenses, sales, invoices, insurance in force, etc. Brands of T. C. Williams and British-American are included.
    - Cost Sheets, 1906 Apr.-1907 Sept. (Volume 78)
    - Cost Sheets, 1907 Oct.-1908 Nov. (Volume 79)
      (Additional reports of 1907 Oct. are in the combined Invoice Book, 1908 Jan.-Feb. of Dunlop,; Williams, and British-American)
    - Cost Sheets, 1908 Dec.-1910 Feb. (Volume 80)
    - Cost Sheets, 1910 Feb.-1911 Apr. (Volume 81)
    - Cost Sheets, 1911 Apr.-1912 July (Volume 82)
    - Cost Sheets, 1912 July-1913 Aug. (Volume 83)
  - Details of Cost
    Usually labeled David Dunlop and Blue Details, these records provide monthly cost figures by brands including the amounts manufactured and shipped and the inventories at the first and the last of the month. The brands of T. C. Williams and British-American are included.
    - Details of Cost, 1908 Jan.-1909 Aug. (Volume 84)
    - Details of Cost, 1909 Sept.-1910 June (Volume 85)
    - Details of Cost, 1910 July-1911 Mar. (Volume 86)
    - Details of Cost, 1911 Apr.-1912 Jan. (Volume 87)
    - Details of Cost, 1912 Jan.-Sept. (Volume 88)
    - Details of Cost, 1912 Oct.-1913 Mar.; 1913 Dec.; 1915 Apr. (Volume 89)
    - Details of Cost, 1913 Apr.-Nov. (Volume 90)
  - General Statements
    A considerable variety of reports, some monthly and many weekly, are included, such as: inventories of leaf; insurance in force; strips used for each brand; reports to Traffic Dept. on shipments, supplies, and leaf received; brands in use and not in use; tags in use; purchases; and various transactions.
    - General Statements, 1904 July-1905 Sept. (Volume 91)
    - General Statements, 1905 Aug.-1906 July (Volume 92)
    - General Statements, 1910 Feb.-1911 Oct. (Volume 93)
    - General Statements, 1911 Oct.-1913 May (Volume 94)
    - A folder of miscellaneous papers, 1902-1922, includes a few accounts from Dunlop. The folder is filed in the first box of the collection.
    - Voucher Record, No. 1, 1903 Aug.-1905 Apr. (Volume 95)
    - Voucher Record, No. 8, 1923 Jan.-1929 Apr. (Volume 96)
    - Receiving Book, 1903 July-1905 June (Volume 97)
    - Customers Order Book, 1903-1904 (Volume 98)
    - Order Book, 1909 Nov.-1910 Oct. (Volume 99)
    - Order Book with Amsterdam Supply Co. of New York City, 1910 May-1911 Oct. (Volume 100)
    - Checkbook, 1903 Aug.-1904 Apr. (Volume 101)
    - Checkbook, 1904 Apr.-1905 Mar. (Volume 102)
    - Checkbook, 1905 Mar.-1906 May (Volume 103)
    - Checkbook, 1906 May-1907 Nov. (Volume 104)
    - Checkbook, 1909 May-1910 Nov. (Volume 105)
    - Checkbook, 1912 July-1915 Feb. (Volume 106)
    - Checkbook, 1919 Jan.-1921 Jan. (Volume 107)
    - Personal Checkbook, 1917 July-1919 Feb. (Volume 108)
    - Personal Checkbook, 1919 Feb.-1920 Mar. (Volume 109)
    - Brands Stock Book, 1904-1905 (Volume 110)
    - Brands Stock Book, 1905-1906 (Volume 111)
    - Brands Stock Book, 1906-1907 (Volume 112)
    - Brands Stock Book, 1907-1908 (Volume 113)
    - Brands Stock Book, 1908-1909 (Volume 114)
    - Brands Stock Book, 1910 (Volume 115)
    - Brands Stock Book, 1911 (Volume 116)
    - Brands Stock Book, 1912 (Volume 117)
    - Stock of Redried Leaf, 1903-1905 (Volume 118)
    - Stock of Redried Leaf, 1904-1905 (Volume 119)
    - Stock of Redried Leaf, 1904-1905 (Volume 120)
  - Leaf Department
    Volumes listed here are only those specifically labeled Leaf Department or those belonging to a series in which one or more books are so labeled. Accounts from the Leaf Department are incorporated in other account books not listed in this group.
    - Ledger, 1903 Aug.-1904 Dec. (Volume 121)
    - Ledger, 1905 May-1907 Mar. (Volume 122)
    - Ledger, 1907 Apr.-1908 Dec. (Volume 123)
    - Ledger, 1909 Jan.-1911 Jan. (Volume 124)
    - Ledger, 1917-1923 (Volume 125)
    - Journal, 1903 Aug.-1905 May (Volume 126)
    - Journal, 1907 May-1910 Feb. (Volume 127)
    - Journal, 1910 Mar.-1911 Jan. (Volume 128)
    - Journal, 1916 Dec.-1923 June (Volume 129)
  - Statements
    One of these volumes is labeled Invoices, but Statements seems a better designation, because they, like Dunlop's cost sheets and general statements, include a variety of weekly and monthly reports as well as invoices and records of transactions for a particular day. The reports include trial balances, inventories, invoices, purchases, expenses, insurance in force, costs, and other data.
    - Statements, 1911 Feb.-Nov. (Volume 130)
    - Statements, 1912 July-1913 May (Volume 131)
    - Statements, 1913 Apr.-Dec. (Volume 132)
    - Statements, 1913 Dec.-1914 Aug. (Volume 133)
    - Receiving Book, 1911-1914 (Volume 134)
    - Receiving Book, 1914-1918 (Volume 135)
    - Voucher Record for Leaf Tobacco Received, No. 1, 1911 Feb.-1915 July (Volume 136)
    - Voucher Record for Leaf Tobacco Received, No. 2, 1915 Aug.-1919 Oct. (Volume 137)
    - Pickings Book, 1910-1912 (Volume 138)
    - Pickings Book, 1914-1919 (Volume 139)
    - Machinery and Fixtures Inventory, 1911-1914 (Volume 140)
    - Payroll Book, 1915 Sept. 29 (Volume 141)
    - Insurance Record Book, 1905-1907 (Volume 142)
    - Insurance Record Book, 1906-1911 (Volume 143)
    - Insurance Record Book, 1912-1916 (Volume 144)
    - Insurance Values, 1911-1913 (Volume 145)
    - Insurance Values, 1914-1916 (Volume 146)
    - Memorandum of Insurance Changes, 1907-1908, and Free Materials Received and Permits, 1902-1907 (Volume 59)
      (Included in Dunlop's Shipments to C. R. Somervail & Co., 1901
    - Order Book Upon Supply Dept. of British-American Tobacco Co., 1912-1923 (Volume 147)
    - Stock Book, 1913-1914 (Volume 148)
    - Wrapper Stock Book, 1913 (Volume 149)
    - Wrapper Stock Book, 1913-1915 (Volume 150)
    - Old Street Stemmery Stock Book, 1909-1912 (Volume 151)
    - Old Street Stemmery Picking Room Stock Book, 1911 (Volume 152)
  - Warehouse Storage Books
    The indices and contents of the Storage Books for Warehouses, 1907-1911, and of the Insurance Record Books are useful in identifying the various warehouses represented by the Storage Books. These volumes were kept by years of storage, but crop years were also recorded.
    - Storage Book for Warehouses, 1907-1911 (Volume 153)
    - Storage Book for Arrington, Sect. 1, 1910-1913 (Volume 154)
    - Storage Book for Arrington, Sect. 1, 1912-1914 (Volume 155)
    - Storage Book for Arrington, Sect. 1, 1912-1914 (Volume 156)
    - Storage Book for Arrington, Sect. 2, 1910-1914 (Volume 157)
    - Storage Book for Arrington, Sect. 2, 1912-1914 (Volume 158)
    - Storage Book for Arrington, Sect. 3, 1909-1914 (Volume 159)
    - Storage Book for Arrington, Sect. 3, 1910-1914 (Volume 160)
    - Storage Book for Arrington, Sect. 3, 1912-1914 (Volume 161)
    - Storage Book for Brown St., Northern Sect., 1908-1911 (Volume 162)
    - Storage Book for Brown St., Southern Sect. 1908-1911 (Volume 163)
    - Storage Book for Cockade City Shed, No. 1, 1910-1913 (Volume 164)
    - Storage Book for Cockade City Shed, No. 2, 1912-1914 (Volume 165)
    - Storage Book for Cockade City Shed, No. 3, 1912-1913 (Volume 166)
    - Storage Book for Cockade City Shed, No. 4, 1913-1914 (Volume 167)
    - Storage Book for Cockade City Shed, No. 5, 1913-1914 (Volume 168)
    - Storage Book for Cockade City Shed, No. 6, 1912-1913 (Volume 169)
    - Storage Book for Cockade City Shed, No. 7, 1912-1913 (Volume 170)
    - Storage Book for Cockade City Shed, No. 8, 1912-1913 (Volume 171)
    - Storage Book for Cockade City Shed, No. 9, 1913 (Volume 172)
    - Storage Book for Cockade City Shed, No. 11, 1913 (Volume 173)
    - Storage Book for Cockade City Shed, No. 15, 1913-1914 (Volume 174)
    - Storage Book for Cockade City Shed, No. 16, 1913-1914 (Volume 175)
    - Storage Book for Oaks, 1913 (Volume 176)
    - Storage Book for Oaks and Virginia, 1909-1913 (Volume 177)
    - Storage Book for Old St., No. 1, 1911 (Volume 178)
    - Storage Book for Old St., No. 1, 1912-1913 (Volume 179)